A Guide to the Colonial Papers, 1630-1778
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Chronological Files, 1630-1778., Extent: 8 boxes. (Box 142-149)
  - 1691
    - May 1
      - Letter of John West (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 8))
      - Certificate of Jahleel Brenton (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 25))
    - May 7 - Resolution of the House of Burgesses (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 9))
    - May 16 - Proceedings of the Council (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 10))
    - May 22 - Deposition of Walter Cocke (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 11))
    - May
      - Petition of Henry Gauler (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 12))
      - Petition of Sarah Wilson (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 13))
      - Petition of Thomas Busbey (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 14))
    - June 3 - Account of James Crabtree (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 29))
    - June 4
      - Petition of Henry Jenkins (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 15))
      - Letter of Isaac Foxcroft to Gov. Francis Nicholson (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 16))
    - June 16 - Petition of Ruth Fulcher (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 17))
    - June 23 - Protest by Capt. John Lean (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 18))
    - Oct. 2 - Receipt of Philip Lightfoot (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 19))
    - Oct. 7 - Proceedings of the Stafford County Court (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 19a-b))
    - Oct. 28 - Bond of William Trenow (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 20))
    - Oct. 29 - Order of the Lieutenant Governor Francis Nicholson (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 21))
    - Oct. 29 - Order of the Lieutenant Governor Francis Nicholson (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 21))
    - Oct. 30
      - Deposition of James Lamount (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 22))
      - Opinion of E. Chilton (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 23))
    - Nov. 5 - Proceedings of the Council (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 24))
    - Dec. 15 - Proceedings of the Isle of Wight County Court (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 24a))
    - n.d.
      - Petition of William Digges (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 26))
      - Petition of William Chichester (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 27))
      - Petition of Joseph Bridger (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 28))
      - Account of James Crabtree (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 29))
      - Petition of Malachy Peale (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 30))
      - Petition of Daniel Wade (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 31))
  - 1691/1692 & 1692
    - Account of James Grey (Box 142, Folder 8 (Item 34))
    - Jan. 13 - Account of William Byrd, Auditor (See Oversized) (Box 143, Folder 8 (Item 43a))
    - Jan. 23 - Writs of Summons of Miles Cary (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 1))
    - Feb. 9 - Proceedings of Isle of Wight County Court (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 32a))
    - Feb. 10 - Writ of Summons to James Waugh (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 2))
    - Mar. 3 - Message of Thomas Milner, Speaker of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 3))
    - Mar. 8 - Address of Thomas Milner, Speaker of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 4))
    - Mar. 16
      - Writ of Summons of William Edwards (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 5))
      - Petition of Thomas Wilkinson (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 6))
    - Mar. 17 - Petition of John Fountain (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 8))
    - Mar. 21 - Writ of Summons of Miles Cary (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 9))
    - Mar. 23 - Writ of Summons of Miles Cary (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 10))
    - Mar. 24 - Account of William Byrd, Auditor (See Oversized) (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 45a))
    - Mar. 30 - Writ of Summons of Miles Cary (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 11))
    - Mar. 31 - Order of the Lieutenant Governor & Council (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 12))
    - Apr. 1
      - Order of the Lieutenant Governor (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 13))
      - Writ of Summons for a Jury (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 14))
      - Writs of Summons of Miles Cary (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 16))
    - Apr. 2 - Writ of Summons for a Jury (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 15))
    - Apr. 4 - Proceedings of the General Court (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 17))
    - Apr. 7 - Writ of Summons to William Hooper (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 18))
    - Apr. 8 - Order to Sheriff of Charles City County (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 19))
    - Apr. 11 - Writ of Summons of Miles Cary (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 20))
    - Apr. 12
      - Writ of Summons of Miles Cary (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 21))
      - Writ of Summons of Miles Cary (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 22))
    - Apr. 18 - Writ of Summons to Thomas Barber (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 23))
    - Apr. 20 - Deposition of John Corprew (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 24))
    - Apr. 21 - Petition of Francis Foxcraft (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 24))
    - Apr. 25
      - Proceedings of the Council of State (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 26))
      - List of Thomas Barber, Sheriff of York County (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 27))
    - Apr.
      - Proceedings of the General Court (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 28))
      - Petition of Lt. David Straughan and Rangers (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 28a))
    - June 22 - Petition of Francis Nicholson, et al. (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 29))
    - June 23 - Opinions of Edward Chillon, Attorney General (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 30))
    - June - Petition of James Batty (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 31))
    - July 5 - Protest of Capt. Thomas Sawyer (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 32))
    - Sept. 20 - Declaration of Sir Edmund Andros (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 33))
    - Oct. 21 - Orders of Sir Edmund Andros (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 34))
    - Oct. 24
      - Proceedings of the Council of State (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 43))
      - Order of the General Court (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 45))
    - Oct. 26 - Letter of Giles Webb (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 35))
    - Oct. 31
      - Letter of John Taliaferro (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 36))
      - Journal of the services of the Rangers on the Potomac under David Straughan (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 37))
      - Order of the General Court (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 44))
    - Nov. 1 - Order of the General Court (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 38))
    - Nov. 2 - David Straughan's request for pay (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 39))
    - Nov. 4
      - Accounts of Thomas Smith (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 40))
      - Letter of Thomas Smith (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 41))
    - Dec. 23 - Proceedings of Council (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 43))
    - n.d.
      - Petition of Edmund Jenings (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 46))
      - Writ of Summons of William Edwards (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 47))
      - Account of Rangers (Box 143, Folder 9 (Item 48))
  - 1693
    - May 1 - Proceedings of the Essex County Court & General Court (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 2))
    - May 9 - Account of Edmund Randolph (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 3))
    - May 15 - Note of executed orders by George Parke (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 4))
    - May 19 - Proceedings of the Stafford County Court (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 5))
    - Aug. 31 - Petition of William Churchill (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 6))
    - Oct. 31 - Address of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 7))
    - Nov. 11 - Address of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 8))
    - Nov. 13 - Address of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 9))
    - Nov. 19 - Address of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 10))
    - Dec. 10 - Bond of Capt. Hornby (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 11))
    - n.d.
      - Petition of Edward Ross (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 12))
      - Summons of Governor Lionel Copley of Maryland (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 13))
  - 1693/1694 Jan. 8 - Obligation signed by Thomas Carpenter & Richard Nusum (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 14))
  - 1695
    - May 6
      - Address to the Governor & Council (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 16))
      - Proceedings of the Vestry of St. John's Parish (See Oversized) (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 17))
      - Letter from George Robinson to the Governor (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 20))
    - May 18
      - Address of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 18))
      - Address of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 19))
  - 1696
    - Jan. 15 - Return of the Sheriff of Lancaster County (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 1))
    - Sept. 22 - Depositions of Henry Wriothesley, John Freeman, Alexander Lumley, & Richard Beard (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 21))
    - Oct. 1 - Petition of Inhabitants of Pamunkey Neck (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 22))
    - Oct. 6 - Deposition of Richard Kilbourn (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 23))
    - Oct. - Bill for Facilitating the Payment for the College of William & Mary (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 24))
    - Nov. 21 - Deputation of Christopher Wormley (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 25))
    - n.d.
      - Report of William Randolph, Attorney General (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 26))
      - Petition of Thomas Ward (Box 143, Folder 10 (Item 27))
  - 1696/1697 Feb. 25 - Return of W. Edwards, Clerk of the Council (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 2))
  - 1697
    - Apr. 8 - Return of the Sheriff of Henrico County (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 3))
    - Apr. 12 - Petition of Inhabitants of Accomack County (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 4))
    - Apr. 26
      - Letter from Rodham Kenner (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 5))
      - Letter from Richard Haynie (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 5a))
    - Apr. 29 - Certificate of Thomas Edmondson (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 6))
    - June 12 - Proceedings of the Council (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 7))
    - Oct. 6 - Proposals of Accomack County (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 8))
    - Oct. 11 - Proposals of York County (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 9))
    - Oct. 18 - Letter from John Ransone (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 10))
    - Oct. 21 - Letter from John Brasseur (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 11))
    - Oct. 23
      - Petition of William Harrison (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 12))
      - Petition of John Hix (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 13))
      - Petition of Thomas Drawcutt (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 14))
      - Speech of Governor Edmund Andros (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 15))
    - Oct. 26
      - Report of the Committee of Public Claims (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 16))
      - Proposition of John Washbourne & Richard Bayley (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 17))
      - Petition of Anthony Armistead (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 18))
    - Oct. 27
      - Address of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 19))
      - Certificate of Christopher Wormeley & Edmund Jenings (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 20))
    - Oct. 28 - Petition of Alexander Newman (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 21))
    - Oct. 30 - Petition of Benoni Burroughs & John Thorowgood (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 22))
    - Nov. 1
      - Message of the Council (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 23))
      - Certificate of Christopher Wormeley & Edmund Jenings (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 24))
      - Petition of Thomas Hodges & Thomas Mason (Box 143, Folder 11 (Item 25))
    - Nov. 3 - Orders of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 1))
    - n.d.
      - Petition & Account of Joshua Broadbent (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 2))
      - Petition of Richard Curtain (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 3))
      - Petition of Capt. Joshua Broadbent (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 4))
  - 1698
    - Apr. 18 - Declaration of Bartholomew Fowler (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 5))
    - Apr. 23 - Order of the General Court (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 6))
    - June 2 - Indictment of Gerrard Sly (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 7))
    - Sept. 2 - Proceedings of the Provincial Court at Annapolis (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 8))
    - Oct. 25 - Letter from William Allerton to the Governor (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 9))
    - Oct. 29 - Declaration of Bartholomew Fowler (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 10))
    - Nov. 5
      - Order to the Auditor (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 11))
      - Order to the Auditor (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 12))
    - Nov. - Warrant of the Commissioners of the Treasury (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 13))
  - 1699
    - Feb. 10 - Letter of King William III (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 14))
    - Mar. 28 - Letter of Gov. Francis Nicholson (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 15))
    - Apr. 12 - Letter from the Stafford County Court (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 16))
    - Apr. 15 - Endorsement Page of a letter from Gov. Blackiston, Maryland (originally filed in Folder 10) (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 15))
    - Apr. 21 - Letter of Giles Vanderasteal & Burr Harrison (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 17))
    - May 2 - Complaints of the Occahanock, Nansemond, & Nottoway Indians (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 18))
    - May 8 - Petition of Inhabitants of Stafford County (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 19))
    - June 2 - Address of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 20))
    - July 7 - Certificate of Oaths to Civil and Military Officers (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 21))
    - Nov. 3 - Journal of David Straughan & Giles Tillett (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 22))
    - Nov. 9 - Letter of George Mason (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 23))
    - n.d. - Account of Charles Wells (Box 143, Folder 12 (Item 24))
  - 1700
    - Feb. 12 - Account of Dionisius Wright (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 23))
    - May 5 - Certificate of Henry Tyler (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 1))
    - May 19
      - Certificate of Henry Tyler (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 2))
      - Certificate of Henry Tyler (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 3))
    - May 22 - Order of Governor Francis Nicholson (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 4))
    - May 23 - Account of William Byrd (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 5))
    - May 26 - Account of John Rand (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 6))
    - May 30 - Certificate of Henry Tyler (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 7))
    - June 18
      - Receipt of Richard Bayley & Charles Haynes (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 8))
      - Letter of Col. George Mason (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 9))
    - July 3 - Letter of Phillip Hoskins & William Dent (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 10))
    - July 10
      - Petition of Civil & Military Officers of Stafford County (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 11))
      - Proceedings of the Council of State (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 11a))
      - Letter of George Mason (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 12))
    - Aug. 22 - Letter of William Robertson (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 13))
    - Sept. 7 - Returns of the Vestry of Martin's Hundred Parish (See Oversized) (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 14))
    - Oct. 26 - Order of the Council of State (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 15))
    - Dec. 18 - Resolutions of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 17))
    - Dec. 23 - Petition of Benjamin Harrison, Jr. (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 18))
    - Dec. 24 - Resolution of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 19))
    - Dec. 27
      - Amendment to the Assembly's Address to his Majesties by the Council (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 20))
      - List of Warrants of William Byrd (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 21))
      - Account of Expenses of Dionisius Wright (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 22))
    - n.d.
      - Account of Bartholomew Fowler (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 27))
      - Account of Bartholomew Fowler (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 28))
  - 1700/1701
    - March 12
      - Account of John Bently (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 24))
      - Warrant of Governor Francis Nicholson to John Bently (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 25))
      - Warrant of Governor Francis Nicholson to Cornelius (Box 143, Folder 13 (Item 26))
  - 1701
    - Apr. 23 - Account of Edward Ross (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 1))
    - May 29 - Account of William Harrison (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 2))
    - July 4 - Minutes of the Council (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 3))
    - Aug. 2 - Letter of Richard Lee (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 4))
    - Aug. 23
      - Order & Account of Richard Fossaker (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 5))
      - Account of William Holt (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 6))
      - Order of the Council (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 7))
    - Aug. 25 - Order & Account of Samuel Todd (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 8))
    - Sept. 17 - Resolution of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 10))
    - Sept. 19 - Resolution & Order of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 9))
    - Sept. 22 - Speech of Gov. Francis Nicholson to the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 11))
    - Sept. 26 - Resolution of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 9a))
    - Oct. 1
      - Order of Gov. Francis Nicholson (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 12))
      - Order of Gov. Francis Nicholson (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 13))
    - Oct. 20 - Petition of Robert West (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 14))
    - Oct. 24 - Declaration of Dionisius Wright and others (See Oversized) (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 15))
  - 1701/1702 Mar. 8 - Account of John Young (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 16))
    - n.d.
      - Account of several charges (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 17))
      - Order of the Council (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 18))
      - Petition of George Norsworthy (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 19))
  - 1702
    - Mar. 30 - Letter of Charles Montagu, 4th Earl of Manchester (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 39))
    - May 7 - Letter of the Earl of Nottingham (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 20))
    - May 14
      - Message of Governor Francis Nicholson (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 21))
      - Order of the Privy Council (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 22))
    - May 15
      - Resolution of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 23))
      - Order of the Council (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 24))
      - Order of the Council (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 25))
    - May 19 - Amendments of the Council (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 26))
    - May 20 - Message of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 27))
    - May 22
      - Message of the Governor & Council (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 28))
      - Report of E. Jenings & J. Lightfoot (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 29))
      - Message of the Governor & Council (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 30))
    - May 26 - Statement of unidentified individual (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 31))
    - May 28
      - Amendments of the Council (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 32))
      - Amendment of the Council (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 33))
    - May 29 - Order of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 34))
    - June 16 - Estimate of the Ordnance Office (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 35))
    - June 23 - Order of the Governor & Council (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 36))
    - June 24 - Message of Governor Francis Nicolson (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 37))
    - Aug. 20 - Letter of Sidney Godolphin (Box 143, Folder 14 (Item 38))
  - 1703
    - Apr. 10
      - Petition of William Bird (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 1))
      - Petition and Depositions of William Bird (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 2))
    - Apr. 20 - Order of Daniel Finch, 2nd Earl of Nottingham (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 3))
    - May 24 - Oath of Jane Parke (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 4))
    - Oct. 21 - Patent of Samuel Craddock, John Cave, John Eckholls, and William Glover (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 5))
    - n.d. - Extract of the Memorial of James Blair (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 8))
  - 1703/1704
    - Feb. 9 - Letter of Prince George (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 6))
    - Feb. 18 - Letter of Daniel Finch, 2nd Earl of Nottingham (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 7))
  - 1704
    - Apr. 24 - Recommendation of the Council (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 9))
    - May 11 - Order of the Council (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 10))
    - July 6 - Letter of Charles Hedges (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 11))
    - July 19 - Letter of Arthur Allen (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 12))
    - Oct. 15 - Petition of Henry Fox (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 13))
    - Oct. 16
      - Petition of Henry Roades (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 14))
      - Order of the General Court (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 15))
    - Oct. 22 - Account of Richard Lee (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 16))
    - Dec. 13 - Letter of Sidney Godolphin (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 17))
    - Dec. 15 - Proclamation of Governor Francis Nicholson (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 18))
  - 1704/1705 Jan. 22 - Receipt of Valr Mener? (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 18a))
  - 1705
    - Apr. 7 - Bond of John Owen & Thomas Harrison (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 19))
    - Apr. 16 - Account of Miles Cary (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 20))
    - Apr. 19 - Speech of Governor Francis Nicholson (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 21))
    - Apr. 20 - Letter of Charles Hedges (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 22))
    - Apr. 21 - Account of Hancock Custis (See Oversized) (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 23))
    - Apr. 25
      - Account of Hancock Custis (See Oversized) (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 24))
      - Letter of Governor Francis Nicholson (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 25))
      - Account of Revenue (See Oversized) (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 26))
    - Apr. 28 - Receipt of John Gladwin (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 27))
    - Apr. - Complaint of Robert Hyde, Attorney of John & Elizabeth Wills (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 28))
    - May 1 - Letter of Governor Francis Nicholson (Box 143, Folder 15 (Item 29))
    - May 9 - Amendment of the Council (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 1))
    - May 10 - Message of Governor Francis Nicholson (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 2))
    - May 11 - Amendment of the Council (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 3))
    - May 12 - Letter of Solomon Whately (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 4))
    - May 14
      - Certificate of Hancock Custis (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 5))
      - Certificate of Hancock Custis (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 6))
    - May 24 - Certificate of Hancock Custis (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 7))
    - May 31
      - Petition of Edward Ross (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 8))
      - Petition of Shipmasters (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 9))
    - June 2 - Certificate of Hancock Custis (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 10))
    - June 9 - Account of John Gladwin (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 11))
    - June 14
      - Certificate of Hancock Custis (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 12))
      - Certificate of Hancock Custis (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 13))
    - June 26 - Proposal of James Minge (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 14))
    - June 29 - Certificate of Hancock Custis (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 15))
    - July 2 - Bill of Exchange of John Saunders (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 16))
    - July 7 - Bill of Exchange of George Ebbery (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 16))
    - July 10
      - Certificate of Hancock Custis (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 18))
      - Certificate of Hancock Custis (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 19))
    - July 23 - Account of Miles Cary (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 21))
    - Aug. 22 - Petition of William Bird, Robert Bird, Ralph Bowker, William Holcomb, James Baugham, and Richard Carrington (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 22))
    - Oct. 22 - Commission of Governor Edward Nott (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 23))
    - Oct. - Petition of George Clough (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 24))
    - Nov. 1 - Petition of Inhabitants of Virginia & Maryland (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 25))
    - Nov. 2 - Petition of William Buckner & William Robertson (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 26))
    - Nov. 5 - Deposition of C. C. Thacker (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 32))
    - Nov. 22 - Amendments of the Council (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 27))
    - Nov. - Petition of Philip Lightfoot (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 28))
    - n.d.
      - Certificate of Hancock Custis (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 29))
      - Depositions (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 31))
      - Amendments of the Council (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 32))
      - Amendments of the Council (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 33))
  - 1705/1706
    - Jan. 28 - Letter of Nathaniel Blakiston (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 1))
    - Feb. 18 - Letter of Charles Hedges (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 2))
    - Feb. 28 - Affidavit of Robert Bell (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 3a))
    - Mar. 5 - Letter of Justices of Middlesex County (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 5))
    - Aug. 15 - Petition of the Pamunkey Indians (Box 143, Folder 16 (Item 27))
  - 1706
    - Feb. 24 - Order of the York County Court (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 3))
    - Apr. 1 - Writ of Summons of Charles Chiswell (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 6))
    - Apr. 15 - Proceedings of the Council (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 7))
    - Apr. 16 - Supersedeas of the James City County Court (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 8))
    - Apr. 19 - Petition of Robert Carter (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 9))
    - Apr. 20 - Letter of Sidney Godolphin (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 10))
    - Apr. 26 - Order of the General Court (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 11))
    - May 13 - Proceedings of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 12))